<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Diana Mounter</title>
    <description>Web designer and developer with a passion for user centered design, scalable CSS, design facilitation, and team collaboration. Based in Brooklyn, NY.
</description>
    <link>http://example.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://example.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2016 11:45:26 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2016 11:45:26 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Jekyll!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'Tom'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 20:20:56 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://example.com/jekyll/update/2016/08/05/welcome-to-jekyll.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://example.com/jekyll/update/2016/08/05/welcome-to-jekyll.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Jessica Harllee</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve been thinking a lot recently about taking care of myself and being a basic human. It’s so easy to throw yourself into work or get caught up in something on the side that you really want to do. When I do that I don’t eat healthy, I don’t sleep well, and I don’t exercise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m learning more and more that having those things in my life make me a better person at work. I’m better at my job if I can get up and exercise in the morning or if I don’t eat a shitty lunch or something like that. So I’m thinking a lot about that. It’s not really keeping me up at night, maybe more like forcing me to go to bed and not stay up late at night. I go to bed at 10pm, it’s pretty great, and get up at 6am and work out or go for a run. I’m trying be an adult but I think it also makes me really happy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the summer instead of signing up for another weird project or doing more design work on the side, I signed up for a half-marathon and I train for that every day. I think it’s about finding those side projects that maybe aren’t helping my design [directly], but are helping my design in another way. I’m constantly trying to think how can I be a functional human being, and also a designer. I feel like a lot of people don’t think about those things as much. It doesn’t have to be mutually exclusive.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://example.com/design/details/2015/11/25/potatoes.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://example.com/design/details/2015/11/25/potatoes.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>design</category>
        
        <category>details</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
